A Guide to the Island Resources Foundation records FA1200
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Countries, 1853, 1898, 1925, 1935, 1944, 1946-1947, 1949, 1953-1955, 1958-1961, 1963-2016; 2; 29.03 Cubic Feet 73 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box and 1 flat file folder
  - Dominica, General Information, Economy, Development Control, Tourism, 1972, 1976, 1984-1988, 1992-1994, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 328-330)
  - Dominica, General Information, Economy, Development Control, Tourism, 1977, 1983, 1988-1989, 1997, 2003-2004 (Box 35, Folder 331)
  - Dominica, Clippings, 1989-1990, 1994, 1996, 1998-2001, 2004-2006, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 332)
  - Dominica, Agriculture, Fisheries, Coastal/Marine Resources, Environmental Legislation, Environmental Planning, 1971-1973, 1978, 1980, 1984, 1986-1987, 1989-1990, 1994-1995, 1998, 2001, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 333-336)
  - Dominica, Environmental Profile, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 337)
  - Dominica, History, Culture, Historic Sites, Cabrits National Park, Hurricane Hugo Reports, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 338-341)
  - Dominica, History, Culture, Historic Sites, Cabrits National Park, Hurricane Hugo Reports, Photographs, 1979, 1988 Novmeber (Box 188, Folder 2181-2182)
  - Dominica, National Parks Guidelines, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 342)
  - Dominica, Cabrits, 1973, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 343)
  - Dominica, Cabrits, Slides, 1973, 1979 (Box 189, Folder 2183)
  - Dominica, ACT Dominica Ltd., Questionnaire, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 344)
  - Dominica, Dominica Association of Industry and Commerce, Questionnaire, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 345)
  - Dominica, Dominica Association of Industry and Commerce, Correspondence, 1990, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 346)
  - Dominica, Dominica Conservation Association, Correspondence, 1987, 1990-1994 (Box 36, Folder 347)
  - Dominica, Dominica Conservation Association, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 348)
  - Dominica, Dominica Conservation Association, BSP Biodiversity Program Grant, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 349)
  - Dominica, Cottage Forest Industries, Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 350)
  - Dominica, Development Alternatives International Ltd., Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 351)
  - Dominica, Development Alternatives International Ltd., Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 352)
  - Dominica, Dominica Hotel Association, Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 353)
  - Dominica, Dominica Hotel Association, Correspondence, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 354)
  - Dominica, Dominica Hucksters Association, Questionnaire, 1988, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 355)
  - Dominica, Dominica Hucksters Association, Correspondence, 1987, 1989-1992 (Box 37, Folder 356)
  - Dominica, Dominica Hucksters Association, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1986-1989 (Box 37, Folder 357)
  - Dominica, Dominica Hucksters Association, Mini-Grant, 1987-1989 (Box 37, Folder 358)
  - Dominica, East Caribbean Institute of Development, 1986-1994 (Box 37, Folder 359)
  - Dominica, National Development Foundation of Dominica Limited, Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 360)
  - Dominica, Northeastern Timbers Co-Operative Limited, Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 37, Folder 361)
  - Dominica, Partners of the Americas, Correspondence, 1989, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 362)
  - Dominica, Small Projects Assistance Team (SPAT), Correspondence, 1988, 1991-1993 (Box 37, Folder 363)
  - Dominica, Small Projects Assistance Team (SPAT), Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1986, 1989, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 364)
  - Dominica, Small Projects Assistance Team (SPAT), Mini-Grant, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 365)
  - Dominican Republic, 1978, 1992-1993, 1997-1998, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 366-367)
  - Dominican Republic, Parque Nacional del Este, 1973, 1997, 1999, 2001, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 368-371, Folder 1)
    Oversized materials have been removed. Please contact a RAC archivist to view material. FA1200:007
  - Dominican Republic, Parque Nacional del Este, Photographs, 1973 (Box 189, Folder 2184)
  - French Antilles, 1971, 1979-1980, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 372-373)
  - French Antilles, 1971, 1975-1980, 1983, 1987, 1995, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 374-375)
  - Grenada, General Information, History, Economy, Tourism, Institutions, 1979, 1985-1990, 1994, 1997-1998, 2002-2003, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 376-378)
  - Grenada, Clippings, 1985-1988, 1990, 1996-1997, 1999-2000, 2003-2007, 2009, 2011-2013 (Box 40, Folder 379)
  - Grenada, Parks, Forestry, Wildlife, Agriculture, Land Use, Marine/Coastal Resources, Pollution, Historical Resources, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984, 1986-1990, 1992, 1996, 1998, 2000, 2002, 2006-2008 (Box 40, Folder 380-383)
  - Grenada, Environmental Profile, 1991 (Box 40, Folder 384)
  - Grenada, Report: Tourism and Sustainable Development in Grenada, W. I.: Towards Mode of Analysis, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 385)
  - Grenada, National Environmental Action Plan, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 386)
  - Grenada, Carriacou Historical Society, Questionnaire, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 387)
  - Grenada, Carriacou Historical Society, Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 41, Folder 388)
  - Grenada, Carriacou Historical Society, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 389)
  - Grenada, Carriacou Historical Society, Mini-Grant, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 390)
  - Grenada, East Caribbean Institute of Development, 1986-1988, 1990-1995 (Box 41, Folder 391)
  - Grenada, Grenada Chamber of Industry and Commerce, Questionnaire, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 392)
  - Grenada, Grenada Chamber of Industry and Commerce, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 393)
  - Grenada, Grenada Chamber of Industry and Commerce, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1986, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 394)
  - Grenada, Grenada Hotel Association, Questionnaire, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 395)
  - Grenada, Grenada Hotel Association, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 396)
  - Grenada, Grenada Hotel Association, Mini-Grant, 1987-1988 (Box 41, Folder 397)
  - Grenada, Grenada National Trust, Grenada Historical Society, Correspondence, 1986-1995, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 398)
  - Grenada, Grenada National Trust, Grenada Historical Society, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1986, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 399)
  - Grenada, A Group of Concerned Women, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 400)
  - Grenada, National Development Foundation of Grenada Ltd., Questionnaire, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 401)
  - Grenada, National Development Foundation of Grenada Ltd., Correspondence, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 402)
  - Grenada, National Science and Technology Council, Questionnaire, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 403)
  - Grenada, National Science and Technology Council, Correspondence, 1987, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 404)
  - Grenada, St. George's Development Organization, Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 405)
  - Grenada, St. George's Development Organization, Newsletters, Reports, and Publications, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 406)
  - Grenada, University of the West Indies Centre, Questionnaire, 1986 (Box 41, Folder 407)
  - Grenada, University of the West Indies Centre, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 408)
  - Grenada, Willie Redhead Foundation, 1994, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 409)
  - Jamaica, General Information, Historical, Social, and Economic, 1988, 1992-1993 (Box 41, Folder 410)
  - Jamaica, General Information, Historical, Social, and Economic, 1974, 1980, 1982-1983, 1987, 1990-1991, 1993-1994, 1996, 1998, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 411-412)
  - Jamaica, General Information, Historical, Social, and Economic-Jamaica NPA-LBA, National Plan of Action for Land Based Activities, 2000 November 15 (Box 42, Folder 412)
  - Jamaica, Clippings File, 1974, 1998-2003, 2006, 2008 (Box 42, Folder 413)
  - Jamaica, Environmental Framework, Institutions, Planning, and Strategies, 1987, 1989, 1991, 1993-1997 (Box 42, Folder 414-416)
  - Jamaica, Natural Resources, Management, and Pollution Control, 1972, 1981, 1983, 1987, 1989-1990, 1993, 1995-1996, 1999-2000, 2003, 2008, 2011-2012 (Box 43, Folder 417-420)
  - Jamaica, Parks and Protected Areas, 1981, 1988, 1993-1994, 1999 (Box 43, Folder 421-422)
  - Jamaica, Parks and Protected Areas, 1992, 1995-1999, 2002, 2004, 2010 (Box 44, Folder 423-424)
  - Jamaica, East Caribbean NGO Institutional Development, General Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 425)
  - Jamaica, Jamaica Conservation & Development Trust, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1989-1995 (Box 44, Folder 426)
  - Jamaica, National Environmental Societies Trust (NEST), Correspondence, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 427)
  - Jamaica, National Environmental Societies Trust (NEST), Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1993-1994, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 428)
  - Montserrat, General Information, Economy, History/Culture, and Tourism, 1944, 1961, 1980, 1982, 1986-1992, 1994, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 429-431, Folder 1)
    Oversized materials have been removed. Please contact a RAC archivist to view material. FA1200:009
  - Montserrat, Clippings File, 1995-1999, 2006, 2011 (Box 45, Folder 432)
  - Montserrat, Volcanic Eruption, 1995-1998, 2001-2005, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 433-435)
  - Montserrat, Volcanic Eruption, Photographs and Slides, 1996 (Box 189, Folder 2185)
  - Montserrat, Volcanic Eruption-The Price of Paradise, Volume II, "The Adventure", "Spectacular Footage", VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11883)
    Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instructions.
  - Montserrat, Environmental Profile, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 436)
  - Montserrat, National Environmental Action Plan, 1994 (Box 45, Folder 437)
  - Montserrat, Fire from the Mountain, The Tragedy of Montserrat and the Betrayal of Its People, Polly Pattullo, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 438)
  - Montserrat, East Caribbean Institute of Development, 1986-1987, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 439)
  - Montserrat, Montserrat Chamber of Commerce and Industry, 1986-1988 (Box 45, Folder 440)
  - Montserrat, Montserrat Chamber of Commerce and Industry, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 441)
  - Montserrat, Montserrat National Trust, Correspondence, 1987-1989, 1991-1997, 1999, 2005, 2007 (Box 45, Folder 442)
  - Montserrat, Montserrat National Trust, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1985-1997, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 443)
  - Netherlands Antilles, 1964, 1969-1970, 1973-1974, 1976-1978, 1980, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1992-1993, 1995, 1997-1999, 2004, 2007-2008, 2010-2012 (Box 46, Folder 444-447)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, 1986, 1994, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 448)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Environmental Profile, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 449-450)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Kitts: Southeast Peninsula, Land Use Management Plan, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 451, Folder 1)
    Oversized materials have been removed. Please contact a RAC archivist to view material. FA1200:010
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Beautiful Bassterre Committee, Correspondence, 1991-1992, 1995, 1997, 2005, 2013-2014 (Box 47, Folder 452)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Brimstone Hill National Park Society, Correspondence, 1992-1996, 1998-2001, 2003-2004, 2008 (Box 47, Folder 453)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Brimstone Hill National Park Society, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1965, 1979, 1984-1987, 1995, 1999-2008, 2010 (Box 47, Folder 454-455)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Brimstone Hill National Park Society, Mukti-Grants, 1992-1997 (Box 48, Folder 456)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, East Caribbean Institute of Development, 1986, 1988, 1990-1993, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 457)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Foundation for National Development (St. Kitts & Nevis) Limited, Correspondence, 1986, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 458)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Kittitian-American Benevolent Association, Questionnaire (Box 48, Folder 459)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Environmental Education Committee, Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 460)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Environmental Education Committee, Correspondence, 1990-1992, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 461)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Environmental Education Committee, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1990-1992, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 462)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Environmental Education Committee, Mukti Fund Grants, 1992, 1994, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 463)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Questionnaire, 1986, 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 464)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Correspondence, 1980-1984, 1986, 1988-2002 (Box 48, Folder 465-469)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Correspondence, 2003, 2005-2016 (Box 49, Folder 470)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1989-2013, 2015-2016 (Box 49, Folder 471-476)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Organizational Development Plan, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 477)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Personnel and Executive Committee Handbooks, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 478)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Retreat Planning, 1997, 1989, 1997, 1999-2000, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 479)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Island Resources Foundation (IRF) Grant No.1, 1987-1988 (Box 50, Folder 480)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Island Resources Foundation (IRF), Grant No. 2 and No. 3, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 481)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), Multi Fund Grants, 1993-2002 (Box 50, Folder 482)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Nevis Historical and Conservation Society (NHCS), World Wildlife Grant, 1990-1993 (Box 50, Folder 483)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Rotary Club of St. Kitts, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 484)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, Rotary Club of St. Kitts, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 485)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Questionnaire, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 486)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 50, Folder 487-488)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Correspondence, 1998-2009, 2011-2012, 2016 (Box 51, Folder 489-492)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Newsletters, 1990-2003 (Box 51, Folder 493-495)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Newsletters, 2003-2010, 2013 (Box 52, Folder 496)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Biodiversity Grant, 1992-1993 (Box 52, Folder 497)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Mukti Fund, ID Project, 1993-1997 (Box 52, Folder 498)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Mukti Fund Grants, No. 1, 1993-1994, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 499)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Mukti Fund Grant, No. 2, 1998-2001 (Box 52, Folder 500-501)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Museum Development, 1996-1997 (Box 52, Folder 502)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, Museum Development, 1998-2003 (Box 53, Folder 503-504)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Christopher Heritage Society, ID Planning Retreat, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 505)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Kitts-Nevis Association International, Questionnaire, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 506)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Kitts-Nevis Association International, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 507)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Kitts-Nevis Association International, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 508)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Kitts-Nevis Chamber of Industry and Commerce, 1986, 1991-1992, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 509)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Kitts 4-H Organization, Questionnaire, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 510)
  - St. Kitts and Nevis, St. Kitts Horticultural Society, Questionnaire, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 511)
  - St. Lucia, General Information, Land Use and Human Settlements, National Planning, 1978, 1984-1989, 1994, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 512-513)
  - St. Lucia, General Information, Land Use and Human Settlements, National Planning, 1977, 1980, 1986-1988, 1997, 2001-2002 (Box 54, Folder 514-515)
  - St. Lucia, Clippings File, 1987-1989, 1996, 1999, 2004, 2011 (Box 54, Folder 516)
  - St. Lucia, Historical/Archaeological Resources, 1953, 1969, 1971, 1973, 1975, 1979, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 517-519)
  - St. Lucia, Historical/Archaeological Resources-"Reserve the Future", 1996; VHS (Box 1, Tape AV 11884)
  - St. Lucia, Pollution Control, Integrated Rural Development, 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 520)
  - St. Lucia, Pollution Control, Integrated Rural Development, 1986-1987, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 521-522)
  - St. Lucia, Tourism, 1981-1982, 1985-1992, 1994, 1998-1999, 2001 (Box 55, Folder 523-526)
  - St. Lucia, Water Resources, Coastal and Marine Environment, Fisheries-Hydrology, 1980, 1986, 1988 (Box 55, Folder 527)
  - St. Lucia, Water Resources, Coastal and Marine Environment, Fisheries-Coastal Erosion, 1978, 1982-1983, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 528)
  - St. Lucia, Water Resources, Coastal and Marine Environment, Fisheries-Marine Sector, 1976, 1980, 1982-1984, 1986-1987, 1998, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 529)
  - St. Lucia, Water Resources, Coastal and Marine Environment, Fisheries, 1969, 1980-1981, 1986-1987, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 530-531)
  - St. Lucia, Changes in the Sea: The Political Ecology of Marine Management in Soufriere, St. Lucia, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 532)
  - St. Lucia, Environmental Profile, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 533)
  - St. Lucia, National Environmental Action Plan, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 534)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Development Atlas, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 535, Folder 1)
    Oversized materials have been removed. Please contact a RAC archivist to view material. FA1200:011
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Human Settlements, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 536, Folder 1)
    Oversized materials have been removed. Please contact a RAC archivist to view material. FA1200:012
  - St. Lucia, Saint Lucia Natural Resources and Agricultural Development Project, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 537)
  - St. Lucia, Slides, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 538)
  - St. Lucia, Slides, 1973 (Box 189, Folder 2187)
  - St. Lucia, Caretakers of the Environment, Correspondence, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 539)
  - St. Lucia, Eastern Caribbean Institutional Development, 1986, 1988-1991, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 540)
  - St. Lucia, Folk Research Centre, Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 541)
  - St. Lucia, Folk Research Centre, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1983, 1985, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 542)
  - St. Lucia, Folk Research Centre, Mini-Grant, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 543)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Archaeological and Historical Society, 1977-1978 (Box 57, Folder 544)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Chamber of Commerce, Industry, and Agriculture, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 545)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Hotel and Tourism Association, Questionnaire (Box 57, Folder 546)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Hotel and Tourism Association, Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 57, Folder 547)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia National Research and Development Foundation, Correspondence, 1988, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 548)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia National Research and Development Foundation, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1986, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 549)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia National Trust, Questionnaire (Box 57, Folder 550)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia National Trust, Correspondence, 1987, 1990-1992, 1994-1995, 2002 (Box 57, Folder 551)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia National Trust, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1986, 1990-1995 (Box 57, Folder 552-553)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Naturalists Society, Questionnaire, 1981-1982, 1986, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 554)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Naturalists Society, Correspondence, 1987-1988, 1990-1994 (Box 58, Folder 555)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Naturalists Society, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1985-1988, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 556)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Small Business Association, Quesitonnaire (Box 58, Folder 557)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Manufacturers Association, Questionnaire (Box 58, Folder 558)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Small Business Association, St. Lucia Manufacturers Association, Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 559)
  - St. Lucia, St. Lucia Small Business Association, St. Lucia Manufacturers Association, Mini-Grant, 1987-1988 (Box 58, Folder 560)
  - St. Vincent, General Information, Economy, Institutions, Legislation, Environmental Issues, 1984, 1994, 2002-2003 (Box 58, Folder 561)
  - St. Vincent, Clippings File, 1996, 1998-2001, 2004, 2009-2010, 2012 (Box 58, Folder 562)
  - St. Vincent, Agriculture, 1973, 1976-1977, 1983, 1986-1991, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 563-566)
  - St. Vincent, Planning and Development, Coastal and Marine Environment, Fisheries, 1971, 1978, 1980, 1985-1989, 1998, 2008, 2011 (Box 59, Folder 567-569)
  - St. Vincent, Tourism, Historical/Archaeological Resources, 1971-1973, 1986-1988, 1990, 1997 (Box 59, Folder 570-573)
  - St. Vincent, Environmental Profile, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 574)
  - St. Vincent, CARIPEDA (Caribbean People's Development Agency), 1989 (Box 60, Folder 575)
  - St. Vincent, East Caribbean Institute of Development, 1986, 1988, 1990-1991, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 576)
  - St. Vincent, JEMS Progressive Community Organization, Organizational Development Plan (Box 60, Folder 577)
  - St. Vincent, JEMS Progressive Community Organization, Questionnaire, 1986, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 578)
  - St. Vincent, JEMS Progressive Community Organization, Correspondence, 1949, 1987-1990, 1992, 1994-1995, 2008-2009 (Box 60, Folder 579)
  - St. Vincent, JEMS Progressive Community Organization, Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1987-1991, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 580)
  - St. Vincent, JEMS Progressive Community Organization, Mini-Grant, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 581)
  - St. Vincent, National Development Foundation of St. Vincent and the Grenadines, Questionnaire, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 582)
  - St. Vincent, National Development Foundation of St. Vincent and the Grenadines, Correspondence, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 583)
  - St. Vincent, Organization for Rural Development (ORD), Questionnaire, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 584)
  - St. Vincent, Organization for Rural Development (ORD), COrrespondence, 1990, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 585)
  - St. Vincent, Organization for Rural Development (ORD), Newsletters, Reports, and Information, 1985-1986, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 586)
  - St. Vincent, Projects Promotion, 1985-1986, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 587)
  - St. Vincent, St. Vincent and Grenadines Hotel Association, Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 588)
  - St. Vincent, St. Vincent National Trust, Organizational Development Plan, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 589)
  - St. Vincent, St. Vincent National Trust, Correspondence, 1987-1992, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 590)
  - St. Vincent, St. Vincent National Trust, Newsletter, Reports, and Information, 1969, 1989-1991 (Box 60, Folder 591)
  - St. Vincent, St. Vincent National Trust, Mini-Grant (Box 60, Folder 592)
  - St. Vincent, Windward islands Farmers' Association (WINFA), Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 61, Folder 593)
  - Sao Tome and Principe, General Information, 1946, 1986, 1991-1993, 1998, 2002, 2004-2007 (Box 61, Folder 594-597, Folder 1)
    Oversized materials have been removed. Please contact a RAC archivist to view material. FA1200:013
  - Sao Tome and Principe, Correspondence, 1999, 2001-2005, 2007-2008, 2013 (Box 61, Folder 598)
  - Sao Tome and Principe, Natural Resources, 2004-2005, 2007 (Box 61, Folder 599-600)
  - Sao Tome and Principe, Natural Resources, 1989-1993, 1995, 1998-1999, 2005-2006, 2013 (Box 62, Folder 601-603)
  - Sao Tome and Principe, Sao Tome and Principe, From Plantation to Microstate, Tony Hodges and Malyn Newitt, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 604)
  - Sao Tome and Principe, Comrades, Clients and Cousins, Colonialism, Socialism and Democratization in Sao Tome and Principe, Gerhard Seibert, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 605)